Now, if these people were using MERIDIAN from day one, using a simple cheek swab to get their genetic mix as well as their medical history,
we can identify the best antidepressant medicine for them, which cuts down the ten-month-long, tiresome journey
and multiple doctor visits to just the one, giving them the solution in hand.
Now, this $1.1 billion market isn’t just about medicine. It’s also about wellbeing.
So what we do is take the personal profile of the patient, as well as the resulting antidepressant,
and, using the model, define the most optimized journey for them throughout their time taking the medicine.
Our suggestions, such as diet, the activities to do, and risks, are tailored.
We’ve done extensive research through Reddit and interviews with multiple professionals,
and we’ve found that many people get constantly prescribed the wrong medicine, and that causes severe side effects.
These medical professionals explained to us that the method of approach is trial and error.
On top of this, people spend over $5,000, as well as time spent on medical and transport costs and being away from work.
We can bring that down to just $1,000. Our team is wanting to raise money to build our own kits to send to their home,
and provide all operational costs to make this as simple and efficient as possible for a patient.
Because, as we know, depression is hard, and we want to make it easier. Thanks.